ALEXANDRU STRAMBEANU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+1 (415) 528 0390 eugenalx@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/alexandru-eugen-strambeanu github.com/eugenalx

Full Stack Developer with five years of experience leading both front-end and back-end development, and performing quality assurance. Led teams of 2-6 people across technology, business and design departments.

SKILLS

PHP/Laravel

JavaScript/React/Vue

HTML5/CSS

Python/Flask

C#/.NET

MySQL

Git

EDUCATION

International business law

Master's degree Romanian-American University **Bucharest** 2005 - 2007

Financial management

Master's degree Romanian-American University **Bucharest** 2003 - 2005

Management and marketing

Bachelor's degree

Romanian-American University

Bucharest 1999 - 2003

CERTIFICATES

PHP

SQL/MySQL

Python

Responsive Web Design

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full-Stack Developer

EAC Sheilding, LA Habra, California

March 2023 - Present

- Implement QR code system for inventory tracking using Python/Flask, JavaScript/React, SQL/MySQL, Git
- Defined and implement C#/.Net Module to integrate inventory tracking system with QuickBooks platform
- Defined and developed the responsive EAC Shielding platform using HTML5, CSS3, PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/React, SQL/MySQL, Git
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.
- Develop and maintain relational database

Full-Stack Developer

Dotbite, Vienna, Austria June 2022 - December 2022

- Defined and developed the responsive presentation layer using HTML5, CSS3, PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vue. SQL/MySQL, Git
- Deploy live using Git and Laravel Forge
- Tested websites across browsers, operating systems, and devices.
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.

Web Developer

MaffBags, Bucharest, Romania December 2020 - February 2022

- Developed interactive e-commerce websites using HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, MySQL.
- Worked with clients to gather requirements and develop solutions that meet their needs
- Converting folders with images into database products, ready to be uploaded in Shopify platform. using Python, MySQL, CSV
- Tested websites across browsers, operating systems, and devices.

Web Developer

Nazmie Edu, Bucharest, Romania July 2017 - November 2020

- Developed interactive web application using PHP/Laravel and MySQL.
- Defined and developed the responsive presentation layer using HTML5, CSS3, PHP/Laravel, JavaScript, and jQuery.
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.

Quality Assurance Manager

Alexander Bake Shop, Bucharest, Romania January 2014 - January 2018

· Oversaw operations of the finance department, set goals and objectives, and designed a framework for these to be met.

Financial Manager

Colts Farm & Food, Bucharest, Romania February 2011 - January 2014

• Supervised and managed all operations of a mid-size retail store with heavy foot traffic.